pritikin.com 2019-10-11

# Privacy Policy - Pritikin Weight Loss Resort

#####  Effective 2/12/2009

 **Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**  
Our Commitment To Privacy  
The Information We Collect  
How We Use Information  
Our Commitment To Data Security  
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy  
How To Access Or Correct Your Information  
How To Contact Us

 **Our Commitment To Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

 **The Information We Collect:  
**This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Pritikin website.

On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. On these pages we collect the information needed to fulfill your requests.

We collect non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website.

 **The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive a brochure, become a member of My Pritikin, create a shopping cart account or register for the Pritikin newsletter and updates on our products and services. Information submitted during registration will not be shared with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your request.

On My Pritikin, members often post compelling copy regarding their success and tips for healthy living. We reserve the right to reproduce this copy in full or in part in Pritikin newsletters and other media, but we will never reveal your full name.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

 **Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

 **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**  
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

 **How To Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 305.935.7131 or send us an email at [info@pritikin.com](mailto:info@pritikin.com).

* * *

**Notice of Privacy Practice (NPP) for Protected Health Information**  
This notice describes how your medical information may be used and disclosed and how you can get access to this information. Please review it carefully. If you have any questions or if you need more information, please contact our Privacy Officer at 786.655.8237.
